"use strict";


const STORE = [
    {
        question:
        "What is the characters name in Fallout 1?",
        answers: [
            "The Chosen One",
            "The Lone Wanderer",
            "The Beef Supreme",
            "The Vault Dweller"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "The Vault Dweller"
    },
    {
        question:
        "What year did the bombs drop?",
        answers: [
            "2017",
            "2077",
            "2133",
            "2177"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "2077"
    },
    {
        question:
        "Which Fallout game can you drive a car?",
        answers: [
            "Fallout 1",
            "Fallout 2",
            "Fallout 3",
            "Fallout 4"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Fallout 2"
    },
    {
        question:
        "Who is the leader of the Tunnel Snakes?",
        answers: [
            "Judah Kreger",
            "Vera Keyes",
            "Butch DeLoria",
            "Cliff Briscoe"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Butch DeLoria"
    },
    {
        question:
        "What illness is Caesar suffering from in New Vegas?",
        answers: [
            "tuberculosis",
            "kidney stones",
            "brain tumor",
            "syphilis"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "brain tumor"
    },
    {
        question:
        "What animal did the deathclaws evolve from?",
        answers: [
            "chameleons",
            "wolves",
            "goats",
            "iguanas"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "chameleons"
    },
    {
        question:
        "Who created the Synths in Fallout 4?",
        answers: [
            "The Minutemen",
            "The Enclave",
            "The Brotherhood of Steel",
            "The Institute"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "The Institute"
    },
    {
        question:
        "For what purpose were the vaults created?",
        answers: [
            "Utopian communities",
            "Experimenting on people",
            "Protection from nuclear war",
            "BDSM dungeons"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Experimenting on people"
    },
    {
        question:
        "Who is the GNR radio DJ i Fallout 3?",
        answers: [
            "Three Dog",
            "Bobby Randall",
            "Gob Bluth",
            "Big Joe Mosquito"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Three Dog"
    },
    {
        question:
        "Which famous actor did not voice a character from the Fallout games?",
        answers: [
            "Matthew Perry",
            "Liam Neeson",
            "Danny Trejo",
            "Willem Defoe"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Willem Defoe"
    }
];